Guide to the Undergraduate Affairs, Yale College, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Dean of Undergraduate Affairs, 1956-1987; Accession 1989-A-029
  - Yale Student Groups
    - In-House Archives
      - Yale University Dramatic Association
        - Check Requests and Contracts, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 50)
        - 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - Yale University Student Directory, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - Yalesbians, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Young Israel House at Yale, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - Alpha Phi Alpha--Zeta Chapter, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 55)
      - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - Kappa Alpha Psi Fraternity, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - Kappa Alpha Theta Society, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - Zeta Psi, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - The New Journal, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - Yale Banner, 1971-1985 (Box 2, Folder 61)
      - Yale Daily News, 1949-1987 (Box 2, Folder 62)
      - The Yale Economics and Business Review--An Undergraduate Publication, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 63)
      - The (Yale) Herald--An Undergraduate Newspaper--Publicity, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 64)
      - Yale Political Monthly, 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 65)
      - Yale Record, 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 66)
      - Yale Scientific Publications, Inc., 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 67)
      - Undergraduate Course Critique, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 68)
      - Yale Alley Cats, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 69)
      - Baker's Dozen, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 70)
      - Duke's Men of Yale, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 71)
      - Mixed Company, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 72)
      - New Blue, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 73)
      - Redhot and Blue, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 74)
      - Society of Orpheus and Bacchus, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 75)
      - Something Extra, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 76)
      - Yale Spizzwinks (?), 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 77)
      - The Whiffenpoofs, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 78)
      - Ezra Stiles Film Society, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Council on Global Affairs (COGA), 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Council of Third World Women, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Cross Country Ski Club, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Daily World Forum, [undated] (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Democratic Socialists of America--Archives, 1974-1986 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Diego Garcia Support Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Dinner and Debate Association, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Discussion Group for Economic Growth, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Divine Light Mission Club, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Duplicate Bridge Club, 1962-1981 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Edmund Burke Society of Yale, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - EIDOS, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Esfuerzo Unido, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Esperanto Society--Student Chapter, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Ezra Stiles Dramat, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Fast for Kampuchea (Cambodia), 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Federation of Puerto Rican Socialist University Students, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Focus, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Forum on Science and Society, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Freshman Debate Squad, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - The Freshman Fifteen, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - The Friends of the Chabad House at Yale, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Fusion Energy Foundation, Yale Chapter, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - F.U.S.P. (Federacion Universitaria Socialists Puertorriquerta), 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Greek Student Association of Yale University, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Guatemalan Relief Fund, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Independent Libertarian Club, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - India Association of New Haven, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - The Indian Dramatic Co., 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Inter-Collegiate Studies Institute, Yale Chapter, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Ivy Network Group, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Inventors Club of America, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Jazz Piano at Yale, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Jazzmins, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Jewish Student Union at Yale, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Jewish Students for a Democratic Middle East, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Joelle Fishman for Mayor (Yale Chapter), 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Kochavim: The Yale Israeli Dance Ensemble Archives, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Korean Students Association, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - La Rama, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Le Bec de Baz, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Legislative Research Group, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Coalition of Independent College and University Students, Yale Chapter, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Coalition to Save Student Aid, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Co-ed Informal Singing Group, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - College Hospital Aides, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Committee Against Repression in Italy: Yale Student Chapter, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Committee for Contemporary Thought at Yale, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Committee for National Peace Conversion, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Committee for a Yale Crafts Center, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Common Property, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - The Common-Place Society, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Community Outreach--Asian-American Students [Alliance], 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Compass Film Associates, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Connecticut Committee for Handgun Control--Archives, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Connecticut Intercollegiate Student Legislature, Yale Chapter, 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Conservative Party of the Political Union, 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Cottage Terrace Organization (C.T.O.), 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Acoustic Guitar Guild, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - African Famine Relief Organization, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - AJDE Folk Ensemble, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Alpha Phi Omega, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Alternative Association of Yale, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Ananda Marga, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Arab Forum, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Association of Collegiate Research and Communication, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Association of Yale Women Athletes, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Aid to Central American Refugees, Ad Hoc Committee for, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Alfred Hitchcock Film Society, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - American Association of University Students, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - American Chemical Society, Student Chapter, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Armenian Awareness Association, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Art Forum, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Bahai Club of Yale, 1974-1983 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Bangladesh student's Association, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Berkeley College Dramat, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Berkeley-Davenport Film Society, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Bhakti-Yoga Society, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Big Brother / Big Sister, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Black Student Union, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Blue Moon, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Boofa Bagels (A Yale Student Agency), 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Branford Filmmakers Society, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Branford Medical Forum, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - Bulldog Film Society, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - The But Seriously Folks, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - Calhoun Dramatic Association, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - Campus Travel Services, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - Calliopean Society--In-House Archives, 1966-1983 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - Black Athletes of Yale--Archives, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - The Cap Company, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - Caucus for Radical Politics, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - Caucus for Socialist Alternatives, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 172)
    - Chinese Film Society, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 173)
    - Chinese Students Association, 1963-1981 (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - Christian Science Organization--Archives, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - Choro Dadaius, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - Cinéma Engagé, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - Coalition on Budget Research and Action (COBRA), 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - James Bond Film Society, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Liberty Watch, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Little Eleven Conference Coordinating Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Lubavitch at Yale, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Lux et Veritas, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Malaysian and Singaporean Students, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Members of the Philharmonic Orchestra, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - Microcomputer Users Group, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - Middle Eastern Forum, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - Minority Allied Health Organization, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - Minority Business Association Archives, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - Minority Pre-Med Society, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations, undated (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - Mobilization for Survival, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - The Multitones, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - National Chicano Health Organization Chapter at Yale, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - Native American Support Group, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - New American Movement (Yale Chapter), 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - New Haven Country Dance, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - New Haven Labor Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - The New Theatre Company, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - New World Films, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - (Yale) Numismatics Society, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - One-Earth Magazine, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - Onstage, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - Organization to Sponsor a Medieval Fair, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - Organization for United Action, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - The Other Cloth Trading Co., 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - Outdoor Club Sports, Yale, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - Palestine Forum, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - Pasteboard Players, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Phi Beta Kappa: Alpha of Connecticut, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Phi Gamma Delta, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Photographic Review, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Poison Ivy, 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Political Action Group, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 214)
    - The Politics of Food Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - Progressive Party of the Political Union, 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - Progressive Study Group, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - Puerto Rican Women's Association, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - The Pundits, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - RBD T-shirts, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - The Roller Skating Club, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - St. Anthony Hall, 1956-1982 (Box 3, Folder 222)
    - Saybrook Stereo, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 223)
    - Saybrook Players, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - Scholar of the House Project, undated (Box 3, Folder 225)
    - Scientists for Social Responsibility, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 226)
    - Scoring Club, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 227)
    - Scottish Country Dance Group, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 228)
    - Senior Class Council, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - Senior Class Quarter Century Gift Fund, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 230)
    - Seventeen Hundred and One Club, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 231)
    - Seventh Day Adventists at Yale, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - Shadowbox (The Black Repertory Theater at Yale), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 233)
    - Shr Jung T'ai Chi Chuan Group, Yale, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 234)
    - The Sierra Club at Yale Committee, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 235)
    - Silhouette Films, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 236)
    - Silliman Dookey Society, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 237)
    - Sisters at Yale, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 238)
    - Skating Agency, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 239)
    - Social Environmental Action League (S.E.A.L.), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 240)
    - Society for Combat Exercises and Survival Training, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 241)
    - South Asia Club, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 242)
    - South-Asian Politics Discussion Group, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 243)
    - South and Southeast Asia Students Association, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 244)
    - Southern Africa Solidarity Committee, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 245)
    - Spartacus Youth League, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 246)
    - Speleological Society, Yale, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 247)
    - Spider Films, International, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 248)
    - Sprini Festival Organization Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 249)
    - Star Trek Association for Revival (S.T.A.R.), Yale Branch of the, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 250)
    - Steady Work, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 251)
    - Student Entertainment Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 252)
    - Student Poll Services, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 253)
    - Students for Alcohol Awareness, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 254)
    - Students for a Clerical Union at Yale, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 255)
    - John Anderson for President: Yale Student Chapter, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 256)
    - Students for Baker, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 257)
    - Birch Bayh, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 258)
    - Students for George Bush, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 259)
    - Students for Carter, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 260)
    - Students for Carter-Mondale, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 261)
    - Church for President, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 262)
    - Students for Chris Dodd, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 263)
    - President Ford Campaign on Campus, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 264)
    - Harris for President Committee, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 265)
    - Young Democrats at Yale Committee for Kennedy, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 266)
    - Student Coalition Against Racism, Yale, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 267)
    - Students for Lieberman, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 268)
    - Students for Longyear, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 269)
    - Students for Lubavitch, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 270)
    - McCarthy '76 Yale Student Chapter, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 271)
    - Students for Bruce Morrison, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 272)
    - Students for Reagan, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 273)
    - Students for Gloria Schaffer, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 274)
    - Students for the Exploration and Development of Space, Yale Chapter--SEDS, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 275)
    - Students for Life (Yale Chapter), 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 276)
    - Students Opposed to Intervention in El Salvador, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 277)
    - Study Group on Palestine, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 278)
    - Sub-Aqua Club, Yale, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 279)
    - Sun Day at Yale, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 280)
    - Sunday Papers Group, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 281)
    - Super Speed Reading Course, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 282)
    - Suppertime: A Literary Table-Tent, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 283)
    - Support Group for the UFW, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 284)
    - Students International Meditation Society, 1969-1981 (Box 3, Folder 285)
    - Outdoor Corps, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 286)
    - Tai Chi Chuan Hwa Yu Group, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 287)
    - Taiwanese Society, 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 288)
    - Theater That, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 289)
    - The Third World Photographers Collective, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 290)
    - The Organization of Democrats at Yale (T.O.D.A.Y.), 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 291)
    - The Tory Party of the Yale Political Union Including the "Whig" Party, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 292)
    - Wechi-Karate Blue Club, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 293)
    - Ukranian Club, Yale, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 294)
    - Undergraduate Legal Project, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 295)
    - Undergraduate Literary Forum, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 296)
    - Undergraduate Schools Committee, 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 297)
    - United Farm Workers, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 298)
    - Urban Affairs Task Force (Yale Student Chapter), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 299)
    - U.S. China Peoples Friendship Association--New Haven, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 300)
    - The Used Bookstore (TUBS), 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 301)
    - Varsity Debate Squad, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 302)
    - VAY (Voyeur's Alliance at Yale), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 303)
    - Wildlife Society, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 304)
    - Women's Athletic Association, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 305)
    - Women's Transit Authority, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 306)
    - Women's Words, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 307)
    - Woodwind Quintet, Yale College, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 308)
    - Woody Allen--Comedy Film Society, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 309)
    - World Federalists Association, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 310)
    - Yale Aviation, 1974-1982 (Box 3, Folder 311)
    - Yale Bach Society, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 312)
    - Yale Bible Fellowship, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 313)
    - Yale Bicentennial Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 314)
    - Yale Bokonist Society, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 315)
    - Yale Broadside Magazine, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 316)
    - The Yale Bullpups, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 317)
    - Yale Charismatic Organization, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 318)
    - Yale College Ensemble, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 319)
    - Yale Community Action Group, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 320)
    - Yale Committee of Inquiry, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 321)
    - Yale Concert / Event Committee, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 322)
    - Yale Concert Dancers, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 323)
    - Yale Diplomacy League, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 324)
    - Yale Efforts For Legislative Progress, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 325)
    - Yale Feature Films, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 326)
    - Yale Folk Music Society, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 327)
    - Yale for Udall, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 328)
    - Yale Revue (Publication), 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 329)
    - Yale Frisbee Club, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 330)
    - Yale Jazz Ensemble, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 331)
    - Yale International Folkdance Society, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 332)
    - Yale Labor Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 333)
    - Yale Libertarian Alternative, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 334)
    - Yale Men's Field Hockey Club, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 335)
    - Yale-New Haven Southern Africa Committee, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 336)
    - Yale-New Haven Zendo, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 337)
    - The Yale Petard, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 338)
    - Yale Political Journal, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 339)
    - Yale Polo Association, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 340)
    - The Yale Quarterly, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 341)
    - Yale Ragtime Society, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 342)
    - Yale Romanov Society, undated (Box 3, Folder 343)
    - The Yale Shumash Project, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 344)
    - The Yale Silly Party, undated (Box 3, Folder 345)
    - Yale Slavic Club, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 346)
    - Yale Solar Coalition, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 347)
    - Yale Student Cake Agency, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 348)
    - Yale Student Distribution Agency, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 349)
    - Yale Student Energy Coalition, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 350)
    - Yale Student Magazine Agency, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 351)
    - Yale Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry Archives, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 352)
    - Yale Student T-shirt Agency, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 353)
    - Yale Student Zen Group, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 354)
    - Yale Students Against Cults, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 355)
    - Yale Students Against Nuclear Energy, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 356)
    - Yale Turkish Association, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 357)
    - Yale Tutoring Agency, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 358)
    - Yale Ultimate Frisbee, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 359)
    - Yale Union, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 360)
    - Yale University Rifle Club and Varsity Rifle Team, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 361)
    - Yale Whistling Society, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 362)
    - Yale Whitewater Affiliation, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 363)
    - Yale Women's Crew, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 364)
    - Yale Women's Forum, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 365)
    - Yale Young Republicans, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 366)
    - Young Americans for Freedom, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 367)
    - Young Democrats at Yale, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 368)
    - Young Libertarian Alliance of Yale, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 369)
    - Young Socialist Alliance, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 370)
    - Young Socialists Club, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 371)
    - Yowsah, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 372)
    - Union for Radical Political Economics, Yale Chapter, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 373)
    - Unification Church, Yale Student Chapter (Collegiate Association for the Research of Principles), 1974-1980 (Box 3, Folder 374)
    - Proof of the Pudding--In-House Archives, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 375)
    - Yale Law School Film Society, 1974-1984 (Box 3, Folder 376)
    - Yale Student Speech Association (Formerly The Yale Society for Creative Discourse, A Student Debate Association) 80-84 Publicity--In-House Archives, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 377)
    - Student Animal Rights Coalition--In-House Archives--Publicity, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 378)
    - El Movimento Estudiantil Chicano De Aztlan, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 379)
    - The Yale Standard--In-House Archives, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 380)
    - Yale Film Society--Archive 1976--Spring 1980, 1974-1980 (Box 3, Folder 381)
    - Ulysses S. Grant Foundation, 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 382)
    - Yale Corinthian Yacht Club, 1974-1982 (Box 3, Folder 383)
  - Office Files and Reports
    - Associated Student Agencies
      - Council Minutes--Archive, 1958-1982 (Box 4, Folder 384)
      - Administration, Finances--Archive, 1974-1980 (Box 4, Folder 385)
      - Problems--Archive, 1974-1982 (Box 4, Folder 386)
      - New Agency Proposals, 1974-1981 (Box 4, Folder 387)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Organizations, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 388)
    - Yale Station Display Cases, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 389)
    - Yale Station Keys and Contracts, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 390)
    - Yale Station Display Cases
      - 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 391)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 392)
      - 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 393)
    - Yale Station [Display Cases], 1981 (Box 4, Folder 394)
    - Acceleration Report 77-78, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 395)
    - Admissions: Class of '83, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 396)
    - Black Students: Freshman Counselors' Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 397)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center
      - 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 398)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 399)
      - 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 400)
    - Associated Student Agencies
      - 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 401)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 402)
    - Athletic Executive Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 403)
    - Bakke Decision Conference, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 404)
    - Black Students, 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 405)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Organizations, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 406)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 407)
    - Funding Requests 82-83 Not Approved, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 408)
    - Requests for Use of Yale Name Approved, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 409)
    - Space: Undergraduate Organizations, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 410)
    - International Student Center, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 411)
    - Calvin Hill Daycare Center, 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 412)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center
      - 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 413)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 414)
    - Black Students
      - Policy, [1971] (Box 4, Folder 415)
      - "The People's Paper", 1971 (Box 4, Folder 416)